[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "More shark attacks occur during the day than at night.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "From which of these areas did the apple tree originate before it was cultivated all around the world?", "correct_answer": "Central Asia", "incorrect_answers": ["Europe", "Central America", "South America"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "One of the factors necessary for the formation of a tropical cyclone is a warm sea surface to a certain depth.  As a minimum, how warm should the sea surface be and to what depth?", "correct_answer": "26.5 C (79.7 F) to a depth of 50 meters (164 ft)", "incorrect_answers": ["5.5 C (41.9 F) to a depth of  100 meters (328 ft)", "15 C (59 F) to a depth of 25 meters (82 ft)", "35.5 C (95.9 F) to a depth of  100 meters (328 ft)"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What film company produced the 1998 American film version of Godzilla?", "correct_answer": "Tri-Star Pictures", "incorrect_answers": ["Universal Pictures", "Orion Films", "20th Century Fox"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Square watermelons are grown in Japan.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Where did actor Dax Shepard grow up?", "correct_answer": "Michigan", "incorrect_answers": ["California", "New York", "Missouri"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Triceratops was a voracious meat eater and would consume hundreds of pounds of meat a day.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This person is given credit for coining the term surfing the internet.", "correct_answer": "Jean Armour  Polly", "incorrect_answers": ["Marvin Minsky", "Tim Lee-Berniers", "Gregory Chaitin"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which country is the youngest independent state to be a member of the European Union? (It has been an independent country only since 1993.)", "correct_answer": "Slovakia", "incorrect_answers": ["Montenegro", "Slovenia", "Cyprus"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Fats are a highly concentrated source of energy. It is estimated that one gram of fat provides how many calories?", "correct_answer": "9 kcal", "incorrect_answers": ["7 kcal", "20 kcal", "4 kcal"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The movie The Da Vinci Code was featured in the 2005 Cannes Film Festival.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What kind of machine does Kip hook Napoleon up to in the comedy hit movie Napoleon Dynamite?", "correct_answer": "time machine", "incorrect_answers": ["microwave", "exercise machine", "clothes dryer"]}]